<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Yuanzhe Shi</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yuanzhe Shi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.126.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 20:20:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloud</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 20:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cloud/</guid>
      <description> ☁️ </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</guid>
      <description> 沸腾的红冷似冰 Summer waterloo Silhouette dance Opacity Summer dream Twilight question Goose pond 请予我无垠长夜一束光 Chemistry building 我一生流亡于自己的王国 Chinese new year 2024 New year 2024 Christmas 2023 十一月秋 23rd birthday 22nd birthday Night city Shimmer 盛夏溽暑 枕边雷雨在酿就盛夏 匆匆那年 旧时约 无从释怀的春色如许 Me 2023 可我残破的春天所剩无几 让子弹迎接着风 Summer begin 暖阳里 彤红洗刷霓虹 打上花火 放生十万个地球 2 放生十万个地球 1 Light cicada and summer 白鸟过河滩 Star blindfold Dream origami My eyes dirty eyes Acrylic marker works Sun and summer University ave@philips Cloud blue Ballet of spring Bubbles Drown “隔了好久，我想看看海” End of day Frozen planet End of summer Christmas 2021 2021 12 22 Death of that girl 云出盈月将照我 正解世界 God of betrayal Cold cup warm sun 内脏间隙 21st birthday 金刚鹦鹉和你按顺序吻我 Apollo and dephne Sea Red spider lily in eyes 1 Cold rose Ningbo impression Journey 太陽みたいなキミが大好きだ Me 2021 Breaking time 等火山喷发的小星球 春暖花开去见你 Sick astronut in love Astronut under sea Astronut love Tree in gloom Red Little match girl Chrismas 2020 Me 2020 Water sadness 20th birthday Shanghai 2020 Caramel star July dream Life Kunqu color Kunqu Spring Waterloo spring Waterloo winter Crowd Sky Moon 1 青春之旅 Christmas 2019 Mobius strip Waterloo nights 心魔 芽 Waterloo sky 湛蓝瞳眸 Flamingo Fall 初秋 19th birthday 再见 Plants Summer 2019 4 Summer 2019 3 Summer 2019 2 Clouds Green light Another sky Bottle Summer 2019 1 Whale error Kubernetes The night before graduating Kitchener rain Hand 1 Mojito Christmas 2018 Our town poster 18th birthday Blue sky May 18, 2018 rainny May 17, 2018 sunny Gloom Hello 2018 Snowball ornament The dinning room Just fall Gear knight 3 d Death Picasso at the lapin agile Seven stories Untitled artwork </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo shortcode gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 01:48:41 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/gallery/</guid>
      <description>Creating a gallery shortcode for hugo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:22:22 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my first post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 20:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m 师远哲 Yuanzhe Shi. A fourth year CS &amp;amp; CO student at University of Waterloo.
I&amp;rsquo;m enthusiastic about computer science, visual arts and chemistry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 20:20:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/archive/</guid>
      <description>This is the archive for the stuff I have done.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
